[Auto-generated transcript. Edits may have been applied for clarity.]
All right, folks, I'm just going to quickly show you how to access the, um, RStudio and R programs that will use for quantitative pharmacokinetics.
Um, this year, there's a slight difference in how we approach things following the, uh, cyber incident.
Um, so first things first, if you are logged in on site, uh, on a university computer, um,
you can go straight to, um, the stats for server, which is the second step that I'll do.
But if you're at home, you need to do this first. You need to log in via the City University Virtual desktop,
and you can find the URL for that just by googling City University virtual desktop come down.
How do I access it? Well, you can do two things. You can access a client, or you can just do it through a through a browser.
Click on there. It'll ask you how you want sign in.
You importantly have to sign in with your at city account.
And then when you do that, it'll usually ask you for your password. I've already signed in once today.
Um. And there we go. It's asking me anyway. Uh, it's my password.
It'll ask for access to your camera, etc.. It will take a little bit of time to, um, to log in.
Any minute now. Okay, there we go.
And then if you just open up a web browser from within that desktop, the, um, URL that you need is, uh, the stats for URL, and that is.
Uh, http s s stats for UK.
And then here you log in again with your activity account.
And then once you signed in it'll ask I've already got a session running.
But you basically you're asked to open a new session one R Studio Pro uh launch that.
And then you're faced with the user interface and you can open up a new script if you like.
Uh, previously, I have asked you to link to my library where I've stored all the packages.
Now, you've actually been given with quite a lot of memory. You can install packages yourself.
The two key things to install when you start doing, um, some work with me is tidy verse.
And then some of you might need some additional packages as you go through, and you'll see those in the notes you run.
Install dot packages tidy verse. You run that and you will see install down here on the terminal.
You can see it flashing through. And then once you have um installed it, you need to remember to call Tidy Verse from your library.
Simple as that. And the rest of the instructions, um, on how to do things are all on the web page.
Great.